MY NOW HUSBAND
LUCAS 26 AND
I
F 25 WERE GETTING
MARRIED
WE DECIDED TO TIE
THE KNOT AS WE
WERE HAVING A LITTLE
GIRL TOGETHER AND ARE
MADLY IN LOVE
SO LEADING UP TO
THE WEDDING DAY
LUCAS TOLD ME THAT
HIS BEST MAN
JACOB WANTED TO PROPOSE
TO HIS GIRLFRIEND AS
IT WOULD BE A
GREAT TIME AND IT
IS A NICE VENUE
TO DO IT AT
I SAID THAT
I DIDN’T WANT HIM
TO PROPOSE AT OUR
WEDDING AS IT IS
OUR SPECIAL MOMENT NOT
THEIRS AND THAT THEY
CAN DO IT SOMETIME
ELSE
LUCAS TOLD ME THAT
HIS FRIEND WAS MAD
THAT
I DIDN’T AGREE
I JUST WANTED THE
WEDDING TO BE ABOUT
US BECAUSE IT WAS
OUR SPECIAL DAY
AFTER THAT DISAGREEMENT
I THOUGHT NOTHING OF
IT
FAST FORWARD TO MY
WEDDING DAY
WE HAD FINISHED THE
CHURCH SERVICE AND NOW
WE’RE AT THE RECEPTION
WERE ALL HAVING FUN
EATING
I’M EATING MY FOOD
AND THEN
JACOB STOPS THE MUSIC
AT THE
DJ BOOTH TO MAKE
AN ANNOUNCEMENT
I JUST KNEW FROM
THAT MOMENT HE WAS
GOING TO PROPOSE
I LOOK TO SEE
WHERE
LUCAS WAS AND HE
WAS HOLDING RED AND
WHITE ROSES WALKING OUT
TO STAND IN FRONT
OF
CHLOE
JACOB’S GIRLFRIEND SPELLING OUT
WILL YOU MARRY ME
I WAS SHOCKED THAT
THEY WENT BEHIND MY
BACK WHEN
I SAID NO
I GOT UP OUT
OF SEAT AND WALKED
OUT
IT’S BEEN 2 DAYS
SINCE THE WEDDING AND
MY HUSBAND CURSED ME
OUT FOR NOT LETTING
THEM HAVE A SPECIAL
MOMENT
I RESPONDED WITH
I WANTED THE DAY
TO BE ABOUT US
OUR WEDDING NOT THEIRS
AND
I AM HAPPY FOR
THEM BUT THE WORST
THING WAS EVEN THOUGH
I SAID NO YOU
WENT BEHIND MY BACK
ABOUT IT
SINCE THAT ARGUMENT HE
MOVED TO THE GUEST
BEDROOM AND NOW MOST
OF MY FRIENDS ARE
CURSING ME OUT ON
ALL MY SOCIALS
AITA